<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Bahram Salehi</title>
    <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Bahram Salehi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description>Hello. This is my page</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bahram Salehi, Ph.D., P.Eng.</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Sr. Remote Sensing Scientist: C-CORE Cross-Apointed Professor: MUN Dep. of Electrical &amp;amp; Com. Eng., Memorial University Captain Robert A. Barlett Building, Morrissey Road, St John&amp;rsquo;s,
NL, Canada, A1B 3X5
Tel: 709.864.6701 * Fax: 709.864.4706
bsalehi@mun.ca, bahram.salehi@c-cire.ca
 Biography Received his PhD degree in Geomatics Engineering - Remote Sensing from University of New Brunswick (UNB) in 2012, Dr. Salehi joined C-CORE with LOOKNorth , a Canadian Centre of Excellence for Commercialization and Research, as a Remote sensing scientist/engineer in 2013.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/people/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/people/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Products</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/products/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/products/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/publications/</guid>
      <description>Refereed Journal Papers * Represents the papers for which the first author is my graduate student 1 . Salehi, B., M. J. Valadan Zoej, M.R. Saradjian, 2008. A Preprocessing Stage before the Feature Extraction Procedure in Classification of Hyperspectral Images Data&amp;rdquo; Journal of University of Tehran, College of Engineering Vol. 42, No. 3, pp. 102-113.   Book Chapter    Dey, V., Salehi, B., Zhang, Y., 2014. &amp;ldquo;1. Dey, V.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/research/</guid>
      <description>Ongoing Research:  Improved SIFT Matching and Noise Removal of UAV Imagery for Accurate DSM Generation Multi-frequency (X,C,L band ) and Multi-polarization SAR Analysis for Environmental Monitoring SAR Compact Polarimetry for wetland monitoring with focus on upcoming Canadian RCM data Terrain Stability and Perfafrost Monitoring in Canad&amp;rsquo;s North using InSAR and Optical Satellite data InSAR remote sensing for water level change monitoring Earth observation and procimal remote sensing for oil spill detection and environmental change monitoring Object-based SAR polarimetry for vegetation and wetland classification Speckle noise reduction in multi-polarization SAR data Boreal wetland mapping based on the OBIA of multi-temporal and multi-source data UAV image processing for forest type classification and forest height estimation   Completed Research:  Automatic extraction of disturbances related to oil and gas activities in Alberta, Canada Very accurate crop type classification based on OBIA of multi-source optical/SAR data Urban land Cover Classification using very high resolution satellite imagery and OBIA Moving vehicle detection and velocity estimation using single WorldView-2 imagery Dimensionality reduction of hyperspectral data Hyperspectral image classification and information extraction   Funding:  Defence Research and Development Canada Environment and Climate Change Canada LOOKNorth (Leading Operational Observations and Knowledge for the North) NSERC Discovery Grant Newfoundland and Labrador Research and Development Corporation Ignite Grant Ducks Unlimited Canada Natural Resources Canada, Canada Centre for Mapping and Earth Observation Mathematics of Information Technology and Complex Systems (Mitacs)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Services</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/services/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/services/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bahramesf.github.io/pages/teaching/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>